augusoft.net 2008-05-11

# Augusoft : Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement 

[Free Webcast Demos](http://u.augusoft.net/index.cfm?fuseaction=1011&CategoryID=6&SubCategoryID=14) [Augusoft U](http://u.augusoft.net/) Meet Us IT Tool Kit | 

Privacy Statement 

It is in our best interest to fully disclose our business policies regarding personal privacy matters. To demonstrate our commitment to your personal privacy, this statement contains our business policies regarding - this website (

), Augusoft U, (

) site - hereafter referred to as “sites.”

 __

**Collected Information**   
At times Augusoft sites contain areas where we require you to enter your contact information. This personal, identifiable information is collected and maintained in our CRM system.

Customers who register to use Augusoft services will be asked to provide contact information such as: their name, company name, address, phone number and email address. At the time you express interest in obtaining additional information or when you register for a Webcast, Webinar or various service offering, we may also ask for additional personal information, such as title, department name, fax number, or additional company information, such as annual revenues, number of employees, or industry. 

Augusoft uses the information to further understand the growing needs of our industry and to tailor presentations accordingly. We may also use the information to contact customers to further discuss customer interest in our company, the service that we provide, and to send information regarding our company or partners, such as promotions and events. 

By sending us your contact information, you agree to be contacted by Augusoft representatives in the future, unless you ask to be removed from our customer database. We will gladly honor your request. Augusoft does NOT collect your information and sell it to other strategic partners, companies or third party vendors. We value the personal information of our customers and will not violate their privacy.

Customers can opt out of being contacted by us, or receiving product, service or general lifelong learning information from us at any time by sending an email to [unsubscribe@augusoft.net](mailto:unsubscribe@augusoft.net). 

Further legal information is available on this site.

| 

Success Stories

**Riverside Community College**  
 **Cyndi Pardee**  
  
In six months of going live on Lumens, our budget increased from $750,000 to $1 million. Augusoft Lumens assisted my staff and me to register 12,000 learners annually, manage and assign 150 instructors to classes on three different campuses with 12 on-site locations and produce 290,000 catalogs each year – all with a staff of three.  
Read More >  
  
---|---|---
